webcammax.com 2009-08-19

# Privacy - WebcamMax

**webcammax.com privacy policy**  
  
**WEBCAMMAX.COM PRIVACY POLICY**

At WebcamMax, your security and privacy is of the utmost importance to us. We take the following steps to protect your personal information: 

**INFORMATION COLLECTED**

WebcamMax collects information provided by you by the following methods on this website; 

  * **Subscription to WEBCAMMAX email newsletter**

By opting to receive this communication, WebcamMax will send you regular emails containing relevant product information, product upgrade information, and any special offers that we think may be relevant to you. 

If at any time you wish to unsubscribe from these communications, please follow the unsubscribe information contained in the emails, or email privacy@webcammax.com with your request to be removed from our mailing list. 

  * **Trial software download form**

By downloading any trial software from this website, WebcamMax reserves the right to request information from you. 

If you do NOT wish to be contacted by WebcamMax after the trial download, then you can opt-out of any subsequent communications on the trial download page. In this case WebcamMax will keep your information on record but will not contact you unless you have another interaction with us where you change your communication preference. 

If you do wish to be contacted by WebcamMax after the trial download, then WebcamMax will send you emails relating to upgrade information about that product, and any other information that is relevant to that trial download. If at any time you wish to unsubscribe from these communications, please follow the unsubscribe information contained in the emails, or email support@webcammax.com with your request to be removed from our mailing list. 

  * **Order process**

Credit card information in encrypted during the ordering process and is deleted as soon as your order is completed. All other personal information (name, address and product ordered) is held to assist delivery of goods (if applicable), and product registration. 

During the order process you have the opportunity to opt-in to receive email communications from WebcamMax. 

If you do not want to be contacted, WebcamMax will keep your information on record but will not contact you unless you have another interaction with us where you change your communication preference. 

If you do wish to be contacted, WebcamMax will send you emails relating to upgrade information about that product, and any other information that is relevant to that trial download. If at any time you wish to unsubscribe from these communications, please follow the unsubscribe information contained in the emails, or email support@webcammax.com with your request to be removed from our mailing list. 

**PERSONAL INFORMATION**

WebcamMax collects basic contact information when you subscribe to newsletter or fill in a contact form. This information will be used for administrative and identification purposes only and will not be shared with our partners or third parties. Personal information is stored on WebcamMax computers and is only accessed by authorized WebcamMax personnel. 

**COOKIES**

WebcamMax uses a cookie to store your visiting and referrer information. A cookie is a small text file, stored on your computer's hard drive, that can be read by our system when you return to our site. 

**GENERAL INFORMATION**

WebcamMax also collects general demographic information about visitors to our site. The information we collect creates a broad picture of our population rather than focusing on any one individual. This information is used to continually refine our products and to identify the most popular areas of our site. 

**ENCRYPTED CREDIT CARD PURCHASES**

If you use a credit card to purchase a WebcamMax product, the credit card number is encrypted as it passes over the internet. Your credit card number is not kept or recorded by WebcamMax or our computers - it is simply passed through to the credit card company to purchase the course. In this respect, buying a course from WebcamMax is similar to a credit card purchase at any store. Neither WebcamMax nor the store keeps your credit card number on file. 

More than anything, WebcamMax tries to treat its customers as each one of us would like to be treated. We value our privacy and we value yours, too. It is our goal to make your experience with WebcamMax a safe and positive experience. 

NOTE: Are you a **webmaster** , **blogger** or **internet columnist**? We will present a **FREE License** of WebcamMax to you if you write reviews of WebcamMax on your own website, blog space or column! **Click here >>**
